<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fight for the Future</title>
    <description>Fight for the Future is dedicated to protecting and expanding the Internet's transformative power in our lives by creating civic campaigns that are engaging for millions of people.</description>
    <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org</link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.fightforthefuture.org/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The FCC sabotaged its own public comments process. Congress needs to stop them from voting to kill net neutrality on December 14</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE: November 30, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;, 978-852-6457&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Yesterday’s Pew Research study led to incorrect reports&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, the Pew Research Group released &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pewinternet.org/2017/11/29/public-comments-to-the-federal-communications-commission-about-net-neutrality-contain-many-inaccuracies-and-duplicates/?utm_content=buffer51f58&amp;amp;utm_medium=social&amp;amp;utm_source=twitter.com&amp;amp;utm_campaign=buffer&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;a study&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;that triggered a number of new reports about issues within the FCC’s net neutrality comment docket. The Pew study, unfortunately, contained a number of serious inaccuracies, and lacked needed context in a way that conflated legitimate grassroots advocacy and organic online outrage with malicious attempts to manipulate the FCC docket with fraud.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The FCC sabotaged its own public comment process for the exact purpose of sowing the type of confusion that we’re seeing now,” s&lt;b&gt;aid Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future,&lt;/b&gt; “They knowingly allowed malicious actors to abuse their system and submit enormous numbers of fraudulent comments using real people’s names and addresses without their permission, and they’ve refused to cooperate with investigations or transparency laws.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;She continued, &lt;/b&gt;“Their goal is to obscure the fact that the overwhelming majority of people from across the political spectrum oppose Ajit Pai’s extreme proposal to gut net neutrality protections. All you have to do is look at the unique comments in the docket that people took the time to draft by hand: almost 99% of them &lt;a href=&quot;https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2017/08/isp-funded-study-finds-huge-support-for-keeping-current-net-neutrality-rules/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;support&lt;/a&gt; existing net neutrality protections. Congress must take action now to demand the FCC cancel its planned vote on December 14. It’s unconscionable that the agency would move forward with such a controversial proposal while so many allegations of serious fraud and abuse surround their rulemaking proceeding.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Here are some key things that the Pew study got wrong:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The original Pew study &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/fightfortheftr/status/935958110509953025&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;claimed&lt;/a&gt; that there had only been 450,000 comments during the FCC debate in 2014. There were closer to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2014/9/16/6257887/fcc-net-neutrality-3-7-million-comments-made&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;4 million&lt;/a&gt;. Pew has since &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/pewresearch/status/936028080996585472&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;corrected&lt;/a&gt; this error after we brought it to their attention, but they have not addressed the points below.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Pew study claims that comedian John Oliver promoted our net neutrality advocacy site BattleForTheNet.com &amp;ndash; to our knowledge that is incorrect. During his viral net neutrality segment, John Oliver &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=92vuuZt7wak&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;directed viewers&lt;/a&gt; to his own page: GoFCCYourself.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The study casts suspicion on legitimate comments using the text from BattleForTheNet.com, noting that 476,000+ were submitted at the same time on July 19. That’s because these comments were submitted as a CSV using the FCC’s “bulk upload” option, a perfectly legitimate way to submit comments to the agency, and in fact the one that the agency &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fcc.gov/restoring-internet-freedom-comments-wc-docket-no-17-108&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;encouraged&lt;/a&gt; groups to use. Pew never asked us about this, or we would have been happy to provide them with the records of this. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The study claims that the large bulk of comments came from “a small number of organizations,” and points to BattleForTheNet.com as an example. However, this is a mischaracterization of what the site is. It’s an Internet-wide coalition effort that has been &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.battleforthenet.com/july12/#participants&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;promoted by&lt;/a&gt; dozens of public interest organizations, hundreds of startups, and thousands of websites, apps, and online communities who participated in the July 12 day of action and other campaigns. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Overall, the study fails to give readers needed context to understand the difference between a legitimate comment submitted through a site that provides a concerned constituent to add their name to a default statement, and comments that were submitted using real people’s names and addresses, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-05-18-fcc-ignores-growing-evidence-of-fraud-moves-ahead/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;likely stolen&lt;/a&gt; from breached databases, without those people’s permission or knowledge. The study seemed to be unaware of the various ongoing investigations surrounding this issue &amp;ndash; including a law enforcement &lt;a href=&quot;https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2017/11/fcc-stonewalled-investigation-of-net-neutrality-comment-fraud-ny-ag-says/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;investigation&lt;/a&gt; by the New York Attorney General’s office. By failing to include essential information about the comments they analyzed, the Pew study offers a distorted view of what’s happening in the net neutrality docket.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 11:03:20 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-11-30-the-fcc-sabotaged-its-own-public-comments-process/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-11-30-the-fcc-sabotaged-its-own-public-comments-process/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fight for the Future statement on Ajit Pai’s ridiculous speech</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE: November 29, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, FCC Commissioner Ajit Pai gave &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/the-switch/wp/2017/11/28/twitter-is-part-of-the-problem-fcc-chairman-lambastes-company-as-net-neutrality-debate-draws-heat/?utm_term=.543522c5c8cb&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;a speech&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; lashing out at net neutrality supporters from web companies to celebrities. The speech comes amid the backdrop of massive and growing public backlash to Pai’s proposal to gut Title II net neutrality protections, with more than half a million phone calls to Congress through &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;BattleForTheNet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; in the last week, and &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://verizonprotests.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;hundreds of protests&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;planned across the country on December 7. Many have &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://theintercept.com/2017/11/27/net-neutrality-trump-breitbart-julian-assange-kim-dotcom/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;noted outrage&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;coming from conservatives, libertarians, and members of Pai’s own party. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fight for the Future campaign director Evan Greer (pronouns she/her) issued the following statement in response to Pai’s comments:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;“Ajit Pai’s lies are becoming more and more desperate. He’s trolling celebrities because he knows he has no substantive argument to quell the growing backlash to his extreme proposal.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Pai’s comments about web companies like Twitter make absolutely no sense. Killing net neutrality will further concentrate power on the Internet into the hands of the few largest companies that can afford to pay. Anyone concerned with large web platforms limiting free speech should support net neutrality protections, which allow startups and small businesses to compete with the big guys, and ensure that Internet users have choices.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Ajit Pai’s plan won’t stop companies like Twitter and Facebook from engaging in censorship. Instead, it will explicitly allow companies like Verizon and Comcast to engage in censorship, and it will let large platforms like Facebook or Google pay them to squash small competitors. Pai’s distortion of the facts here can only be described as Orwellian. He’s citing free speech as his reason for gutting free speech protections.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Still, we have to admit Pai is smart: when old allies in telecom oblige you to introduce a plan the entire country hates, mocking celebrities and saying a bunch of random BS is probably the best option.”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Fight for the Future&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;is a digital rights group known for their role in organizing the largest online protests in history including the SOPA Blackout, the Internet Slowdown, and the July 12 Internet-Wide Day of Action for Net Neutrality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 09:39:41 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-11-29-fight-for-the-future-statement-on-ajit-pais/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-11-29-fight-for-the-future-statement-on-ajit-pais/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BREAKING: First Republican lawmaker to publicly oppose the FCC’s radical net neutrality repeal</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://78.media.tumblr.com/8f68c7fbfcd912502079ffc1d228c95c/tumblr_inline_ozxxaujAeB1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;512&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, November 24, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Susan Collins (R-ME) opposition signals trouble ahead for the agency as GOP Senator joins with two other Maine lawmakers in bi-partisan opposition to FCC plan&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Bangor Daily News is &lt;a href=&quot;https://bangordailynews.com/2017/11/24/politics/collins-pingree-king-rip-plan-to-end-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;reporting&lt;/a&gt; that Maine Senator Susan Collins is the first GOP member of Congress to publicly oppose the agency’s plan to end net neutrality. Republican members of the House and Senate have been silent since FCC Chairman Ajit Pai &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/AjitPaiFCC/status/933009189991079936&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt; a December vote to &lt;a href=&quot;http://mashable.com/2017/11/22/net-neutrality-proposal-worse-than-you-think/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;repeal Title II&lt;/a&gt; net neutrality. Since Tuesday morning Congress has heard unprecedented public &lt;a href=&quot;https://motherboard.vice.com/en_us/article/9kqpav/fcc-ajit-pai-net-neutrality-thanksgiving-weekend&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;outcry&lt;/a&gt; with net neutrality activists driving nearly 450,000 calls to Congress through the BattleForTheNet.com campaign.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Internet providers must not manage their system in an anti-competitive way that limits consumers’ choices,” a spokesperson for Senator Collins told the Bangor Daily News, explaining the Senator’s opposition to the FCC’s plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Responding to today’s news, Evan Greer, Campaign Director for Fight for the Future (pronouns she/her) had this to say:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;“We would like to thank Senator Collins for having the courage to speak out against the FCC’s extreme plan to gut Title II net neutrality protections, and we hope to see more Republican lawmakers join her call for the FCC to protect, not gut net neutrality before the agency’s December 14th vote. Senator Collins clearly recognizes that businesses and Internet users across this country simply cannot afford to be unprotected from anti-competitive practices perpetrated by the nation’s broadband giants. An overwhelming majority of Republican voters support existing net neutrality rules. Other GOP lawmakers should follow Senator Collins lead, listen to their constituents about this crucial issue, and take action to stop the FCC’s irresponsible rush toward a vote.”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since Chairman Pai’s announcement earlier this week, we have seen a huge outpouring of support from across the country. In the last 72 hours, nearly 450,000 calls to Congress have been generated by concerned Internet users through BattleForTheNet.com alone, and today’s announcement shows that citizen pressure is working. When enough people speak up, lawmakers from both sides of the aisle have to sit up and take notice – and that’s exactly what we’re seeing happen today.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 16:06:51 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-11-24-breaking-first-republican-lawmaker-to-publicly/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-11-24-breaking-first-republican-lawmaker-to-publicly/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Net neutrality protests to hit Verizon stores across the U.S. during busy holiday shopping season</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;629&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1196&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://78.media.tumblr.com/7cc7a631f4527badf5191905c7265fe1/tumblr_inline_ozro0ycH3Y1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;629&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1196&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE: November 21, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Angry Internet users will demand that members of Congress oppose Verizon-controlled FCC’s attack on the open web&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Internet users outraged by Verizon-lawyer-turned-FCC-Chairman Ajit Pai’s plan to gut net neutrality are planning to protest at Verizon retail stores across the country on Thursday, December 7th, one week before an expected vote at the FCC. In some cities, protesters will march from Verizon stores to lawmakers’ offices. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The protests will highlight the company’s role lobbying to kill rules that prevent telecom giants from charging extra fees, engaging in censorship, or controlling what Internet users see and do through discriminatory throttling. Protesters will carry signs calling on their members of Congress to speak out against Verizon’s attacks on net neutrality and publicly oppose the FCC’s plan, which is expected to be released this week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See the website announcing the protests here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://verizonprotests.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;VerizonProtests.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ajit Pai’s plan is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.politico.com/story/2017/11/20/net-neutrality-repeal-fcc-251824&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;expected&lt;/a&gt; to contain a “total repeal” of net neutrality protections, posing a grave threat to the future of freedom of expression, access to information, and small businesses particularly for communities of color and low income communities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The December 7 protests represent growing grassroots backlash to the FCC’s plan, which polls show is wildly unpopular with people from across the political spectrum. The events are supported by Team Internet, a grassroots network of nearly half a million volunteer activists spearheaded by Demand Progress, Fight for the Future, and Free Press Action Fund, three of the groups behind the massive July 12 net neutrality day of action that drove millions of comments, emails, and phone calls to the FCC and Congress. &lt;a href=&quot;https://demandprogress.org/team-internet-mobilizing-thousands-of-net-neutrality-activists-across-the-country-to-meet-with-lawmakers/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Over recent months&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; the groups behind the protests have organized thousands of constituents to attend more than 600 town halls and meetings with lawmakers to demand their support for net neutrality. A phone call campaign through &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;BattleForTheNet.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;has generated nearly 250,000 phone calls to legislators offices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the protests participants will be encouraged to take a group photo and tweet it at their local members of Congress. Where possible, protesters will march to a nearby lawmaker’s office and deliver petition signatures. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Protests are currently planned in &lt;b&gt;Phoenix, Denver, San Francisco, New York City, Indianapolis, Miami, Boston, Seattle,&lt;/b&gt; and several other cities across the country. They’re being organized by volunteers in a grassroots manner using email, texting, and social media. Local Internet users can volunteer to host a protest, and then connect with other volunteers in their area and encourage them to attend. There will be a special protest event in Washington, DC, details are TBA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This is the free speech fight of our generation and Internet users are pissed off and paying attention” &lt;b&gt;said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future, &lt;/b&gt;“Ajit Pai may be owned by Verizon, but he has to answer to Congress, and lawmakers have to answer to us, their constituents. The corrupt bureaucrats trying to kill net neutrality are hoping to avoid public backlash by burying the news over the Holiday weekend. We’re taking our protest from the Internet to the streets to make sure that doesn’t happen,” &lt;b&gt;she added.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“While FCC Chairman Ajit Pai has been busy meeting with industry lobbyists and greedy Verizon executives, he should not ignore the millions of people who are joining together to reject his plan to kill off Net Neutrality,” &lt;b&gt;said Free Press Action Fund Field Director Mary Alice Crim.&lt;/b&gt; “People in almost every state across the country have been meeting with hundreds of members of Congress and their staff, organizing others in their communities, and speaking out on behalf of the open internet. They know that the open internet is essential for accessing everything from elder care to mental health services and they&amp;rsquo;re willing to fight for it. This momentum of popular support for Net Neutrality will spill into the streets beginning Dec. 7 as people protest Pai and his corporate cronies outside Verizon stores nationwide. Our message to Pai and Verizon is clear: people everywhere will not sit idle as you destroy the free and open internet.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Americans are sick and tired of lawmakers placing the profits of monopolistic companies like Verizon and Comcast above the interests of ordinary people,” &lt;b&gt;said Mark Stanley, Director of Communications for Demand Progress. &lt;/b&gt;“Outside Washington, support for strong net neutrality is widespread, regardless of political affiliation. Now, with what would be a catastrophic vote by the FCC to repeal net neutrality looming, people are ready to take to the streets in protest and to offer Congress one last chance to answer the question: ‘Do you stand for your constituents’ ability to communicate and connect, or do you stand for Verizon’s bottom line?’”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 07:01:44 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-11-21-net-neutrality-protests-to-hit-verizon-stores/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-11-21-net-neutrality-protests-to-hit-verizon-stores/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Internet activists launch “Democrats for a Fascist Dystopia” page mocking self-proclaimed progressive lawmakers who support reauthorization of Section 702 surveillance</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;474&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;998&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://78.media.tumblr.com/9aef40fd583927103f704ba5b12352e4/tumblr_inline_oz273uVEjg1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;474&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;998&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, press@fightforthefuture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Adam Schiff (D-CA), Angus King (I-ME), Mark Warner (D-VA) targeted by online campaign from Fight for the Future&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Digital rights group Fight for the Future has launched a new online campaign at &lt;a href=&quot;http://democratsforafascistdystopia.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;DemocratsForAFascistDystopia.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, humiliating “progressive” lawmakers who are supporting legislation that reauthorizes Section 702 of the FISA Amendments Act, a law that the U.S. government abuses to conduct mass warrantless surveillance, including of U.S. citizens. Even worse, all of these members have opposed fixing the “backdoor search” loophole, through which the government searches specifically for U.S. persons without a warrant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We are Democratic lawmakers who believe that the best future for our children is an Orwellian dystopia where governments have absolute control over their citizens&amp;rsquo; thoughts and actions through pervasive mass surveillance. That&amp;rsquo;s why we support the reauthorization of Section 702 of the FISA Amendments Act,” the page mockingly states, listing Congress members &lt;b&gt;Adam Schiff (D-CA)&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;Angus King (I-ME)&lt;/b&gt;, and &lt;b&gt;Mark Warner (D-VA)&lt;/b&gt; as “members” of a faux organization, &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://democratsforafascistdystopia.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;“Democrats for a Fascist Dystopia.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Under the heading ‘Our Mission,’ the page continues: “Our goal is to reauthorize Section 702, which would let Donald Trump - and any future president - engage in warrantless monitoring and mass collection of Internet and telephone communications.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A “Who we are” section of the site pairs real quotes from each lawmaker about Donald Trump with satirical endorsements of Trump’s potential use of Section 702 surveillance powers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Mass surveillance doesn’t work. It’s not about public safety—it’s about government control,” &lt;b&gt;said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future, the group behind the page.&lt;/b&gt; “In these times it’s unconscionable for any lawmaker that claims to care about free speech or human rights to support the reauthorization of warrantless surveillance of Americans under Section 702,” &lt;b&gt;she added.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future is encouraging its 1.4 million+ members to oppose any legislation that reauthorizes Section 702 of the FISA Amendments Act without closing the backdoor loophole. If Congress fails to secure this necessary minimum, supported even by Senator Feinstein, a long-time surveillance hawk, members of Congress should let this unconstitutional law expire at the end of the year..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 12:56:14 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-11-07-internet-activists-launch-democrats-for-a-fascist/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-11-07-internet-activists-launch-democrats-for-a-fascist/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The FCC will soon vote to kill net neutrality. But Congress can stop them if they hear from constituents now.</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1920&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1080&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://78.media.tumblr.com/d436328a1bb98afc35934edc5fd4f76a/tumblr_inline_oyg76761TK1v5jbac_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1920&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1080&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yesterday afternoon the House subcommittee that provides Congressional oversight for the FCC held an &lt;a href=&quot;https://energycommerce.house.gov/hearings/oversight-federal-communications-commission-fcc/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;important hearing&lt;/a&gt; about the agency’s current plans, including current Chairman (and former Verizon lawyer) Ajit Pai’s move to gut Title II net neutrality protections that prevent ISPs from controlling what we do online with throttling, censorship, and extra fees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With Capitol Hill’s attention now on the FCC, and Pai’s final plan to gut net neutrality protections &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.techdirt.com/articles/20171023/10383838460/fcc-likely-to-use-thanksgiving-holiday-to-hide-unpopular-plan-to-kill-net-neutrality.shtml&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;expected&lt;/a&gt; in the coming weeks, it’s extra important that Congress gets flooded with phone calls from Internet users telling them to stand up and defend the open Internet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’re also hearing there are key members of Congress considering whether to step in and force Pai to slow down. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.battleforthenet.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;This means best chance to stop the FCC from breaking the fundamental principle that makes the Internet awesome is to pound Congress with phone calls right now.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;You can call your reps easily with just one click here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.battleforthenet.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;battleforthenet.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You’ll see a script on your screen, or you can say something like this:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;&amp;ldquo;I support Title Two net neutrality rules and I urge you to oppose the FCC&amp;rsquo;s plan to repeal them. Specifically, I&amp;rsquo;d like you to contact the FCC Chairman and demand he abandon his current plan.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can also just call this number directly and enter your zipcode to get connected to your legislators: &lt;b&gt;202-930-8550.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you run a website, blog, tumblr, or forum, help spread the word by putting up a sticky post, or use one of these widgets, ads, or banners: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.battleforthenet.com/#join&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.battleforthenet.com/#join&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ajit Pai is expected to circulate the text of his rule killing net neutrality on November 22, the day before Thanksgiving. Once that happens, it will move to a vote at the FCC’s open meeting in December, and it will become much much harder to stop him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s clear that the FCC remains set on killing net neutrality. But Congress can stop the FCC from gutting the rules that keep the web open, affordable, and awesome.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 16:50:37 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-10-26-the-fcc-will-soon-vote-to-kill-net-neutrality-but/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-10-26-the-fcc-will-soon-vote-to-kill-net-neutrality-but/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Democrats who voted for FCC chairman Ajit Pai have been kicked off “Team Internet,” will be targeted with billboards by net neutrality activists</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1264&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1968&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://78.media.tumblr.com/393acc9bccc07905c0fff02c03f73f74/tumblr_inline_oxb6jw0mPA1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1264&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1968&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, October 4, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Joe Manchin (D-WV), Claire McCaskill (D-MO), Gary Peters (D-MI), Jon Tester (D-MT) are among the first Democrats to be listed as “Team Cable” on BattleForTheNet.com congressional score board&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The four Democratic Senators who ignored overwhelming public support for net neutrality protections and voted to reconfirm former Verizon lawyer Ajit Pai as chairman of the FCC are among the first from their parties to be listed as part of “Team Cable” on a prominent &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.battleforthenet.com/#scoreboard&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;“Congressional Scorecard”&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; on net neutrality campaign site BattleForTheNet.com, run by Demand Progress, Free Press Action Fund, and Fight for the Future..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future also announced that they will target these lawmakers in their districts with &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://donate.fightforthefuture.org/campaigns/nnbillboards/#page-1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;crowdfunded&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;billboards informing constituents of their Senator’s controversial vote. The group has previously targeted 9 members of Congress who have publicly supported Ajit Pai’s plan to slash Title II protections, but these four represent the first Democrats to be targeted as part of the crowdfunded campaign.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See a mockup of what the billboards will look like &lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/a/hfsp5&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Every member of Congress needs to understand that you can’t vote against the free and open Internet and get away with it,” &lt;b&gt;said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future,&lt;/b&gt; “let this be a lesson to any lawmaker considering going against the interests of their constituents to support legislation or FCC action that undermines existing net neutrality rules.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The only interests Ajit Pai represents are those of the few gatekeeper media companies that want to charge people more for nothing and give them less of everything,” &lt;b&gt;said Candace Clement, Free Press Action Fund Campaign Director. &lt;/b&gt;“Those in Congress who voted to confirm Ajit Pai did so against the demands and interests of their constituents. Pai stands against an open internet, online privacy, local control of local media and affordable access for everyone. Team Internet will continue to remind Congress that you can’t do harm to the people you represent without hearing from us every day and everywhere. You can’t sell out our rights in Washington without consequences.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“By voting to confirm Ajit Pai, these senators fundamentally failed Americans who rely on, or are in need of an open and affordable internet,” &lt;b&gt;said Mark Stanley, Director of Operations for Demand Progress.&lt;/b&gt; “A vote for Pai was a vote to end net neutrality protections. It was a vote for less affordable broadband service for those who need it most. And it was a vote for greater media consolidation, which will lead to higher costs and worse service for consumers. Pai’s vision for our country&amp;rsquo;s communications networks is overwhelmingly unpopular among the public. Constituents are watching intently, and going forward it is incumbent on lawmakers from both parties to unequivocally oppose Pai and his policies that place the interests of Big Cable over those of ordinary Americans.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Demand Progress, Free Press Action Fund, and Fight for the Future were the leading groups behind the massive July 12 net neutrality day of action, which drove a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-13-update-historic-day-of-action-for-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;record breaking&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; number of comments, calls, and emails, to the FCC and Congress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 13:56:46 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-10-04-democrats-who-voted-for-fcc-chairman-ajit-pai-have/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-10-04-democrats-who-voted-for-fcc-chairman-ajit-pai-have/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Net neutrality supporters descend on DC to meet with lawmakers, oppose FCC plan to gut Title II</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1284&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;630&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://78.media.tumblr.com/6723403a28b6c52515c933c153e3f444/tumblr_inline_owulvwroTL1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1284&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;630&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE: September 25, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;, 978-852-6457&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Dozens of Internet users from across the country are traveling to the Capitol to meet directly with Congress about Internet freedom&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON, DC &amp;ndash; More than 60 Internet users traveling from as far away as Alaska, California, Kansas, and Utah are participating in a unique advocacy effort this Wednesday, September 27 descending on the U.S. capitol not for a rally but to meet directly with their Senators and Representatives in support of Title II net neutrality protections. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The participants, recruited through an &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com/dc&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;online campaign&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;spread through email and social media include small business owners, students, IT professionals, startup founders, single parents, and people from a wide range of political perspectives and representing more than 20 states. Fight for the Future launched a &lt;a href=&quot;https://donate.fightforthefuture.org/campaigns/dctravel/#page-1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;crowdfunding page&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; where net neutrality supporters who couldn’t attend the meetings in DC could chip in to help cover travel costs for others who need assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The companies trying to kill net neutrality are spending millions on lobbyists who are hitting the Hill constantly to spread fear and misinformation,” &lt;b&gt;said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future, &lt;/b&gt;“Internet users, entrepreneurs, and small business owners have such critically important stories to tell about how Title II net neutrality protections directly impact their basic rights and their ability to put food on the table. Tomorrow, we’re harnessing the power of the Internet to make sure that those stories are heard over the noise of the telecom lobby.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;A free and open internet is the lifeblood of small business in America, and Net Neutrality as protected in Title II, is what guarantees that the internet remains free and open,” &lt;b&gt;said Sean Frame, who runs a video production company in California and is traveling to DC to participate in the meetings,&lt;/b&gt; “My business, and the businesses of my clients cannot survive if we are placed in the internet slow-lane while larger competitors buy faster access.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lesley Perg, who is traveling from Minnesota, said&lt;/b&gt;, &amp;ldquo;I am a PhD climate scientist on the American Care Act, an avid backpacker in our National Parks, and I tutor mainly immigrants and people of color in Adult Basic Education and Citizenship. A free and open internet is imperative for a functioning democracy, and if we give away our infrastructure now, I believe it will be difficult to impossible to overturn in the future. Net Neutrality underlies all the causes that are important to me - that&amp;rsquo;s how I picked my battle.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“As a small business owner net neutrality is very important to me to make sure I can compete against large corporations,” a&lt;b&gt;dded Alison Stanton, who is traveling from Illinois, &lt;/b&gt;“ I&amp;rsquo;m scared I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be able to reach potential customers if we lose net neutrality because it would be too expensive to communicate with them.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to Fight for the Future, organizations supporting the Day of Advocacy include Public Knowledge, Center for Media Justice, Common Cause, EFF, Consumers union, Free Press, and Writers Guild of America West. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 14:33:01 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-09-25-net-neutrality-supporters-descend-on-dc-to-meet/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-09-25-net-neutrality-supporters-descend-on-dc-to-meet/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Over 500 small businesses sign open letter to FCC and Congress urging them to preserve Title II net neutrality protections</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;507&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1046&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://78.media.tumblr.com/9dfa83b65e0f533dd63b8599d49a7b35/tumblr_inline_ovk21b1TrY1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;507&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1046&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, August 31, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Businesses from across the US tell lawmakers how losing net neutrality would threaten their ability to reach customers and grow their businesses online&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;August 31, 2017 – Late yesterday, a group of over 500 small businesses and trade associations from across the country signed &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.keepthewebopenforbusiness.com/FCC_17-108_smallbusiness-ASBC-filing-170830.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;an open letter&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; raising concerns over the Federal Communications Commission’s (FCC) plan to repeal net neutrality. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.keepthewebopenforbusiness.com/FCC_17-108_smallbusiness-ASBC-filing-170830.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;letter&lt;/a&gt;, filed with the FCC by the American Sustainable Business Council, warns that “weakening or rolling back the 2015 protections would be disastrous for the country’s business community” who for decades have relied on open access to the open Internet to do business.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The signatories–ranging from dentist offices to sporting goods stores–highlight how the FCC’s proposed changes would put smaller business at a disadvantage with larger companies. Without strong protections Internet service providers (ISPs) would be permitted to block websites, slow traffic, or charge new access fees. The businesses warn policymakers that, “While big companies might be able to afford a pay-to-play prioritized ‘fast lane’ to users, small and medium sized enterprises like ours cannot.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Small and medium sized businesses are encouraged to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.keepthewebopenforbusiness.com/#letter&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;sign on&lt;/a&gt;, as names are being added on rolling basis at &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.keepthewebopenforbusiness.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;KeepTheWebOpenForBusiness.com&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These businesses represent their founders’ dreams for a better life and a better world—and they’re how many families put food on the table and pay their bills each month,” &lt;b&gt;said Fight for the Future co-founder Holmes Wilson,&lt;/b&gt; “The FCC’s plan to end net neutrality puts businesses like these—and the livelihoods of the millions of people that depend on them—in grave danger.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The letter was filed on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/2017/08/30/today-is-your-last-chance-to-comment-on-the-proposal-to-kill-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;final day&lt;/a&gt; of the FCC’s controversial net neutrality consultation, which sparked millions of comments, emails, and phone calls in support of Title II following the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dailydot.com/layer8/net-neutrality-day-of-action-fcc-comments/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;July 12th day of action&lt;/a&gt;. Earlier this week digital rights group Fight for the Future released a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.broadcastingcable.com/news/washington/more-net-neutrality-billboards-go/168195&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;second wave&lt;/a&gt; of billboards targeting members of Congress who support the FCC’s repeal, building on an &lt;a href=&quot;https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2017/08/pro-net-neutrality-billboards-shame-lawmakers-who-want-to-repeal-rules/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;initial round&lt;/a&gt; of six billboards from earlier this month. The ads are currently running in nine different states while lawmakers are back in their home districts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future is best known for their role in the massive online protests against SOPA, the Stop Online Piracy Act, and continues to organize many of the largest protests in the history of the Internet. They recently organized the high profile Rock Against the TPP tour, as well as historic July 12th Internet-wide day of action to save net neutrality. Learn more at FightFortheFuture.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 11:08:06 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-08-31-over-500-small-businesses-sign-open-letter-to-fcc/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-08-31-over-500-small-businesses-sign-open-letter-to-fcc/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cable industry’s own study shows their plan to kill net neutrality is as unpopular as ever</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, August 30, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;While FCC’s refusal to address cybersecurity issues and fake comments creates intentional confusion around data, unique comments are overwhelmingly in favor of Title II net neutrality— by more than 73 to 1&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, the telecom industry is touting &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.emprata.com/reports/fcc-restoring-internet-freedom-docket/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;a study&lt;/a&gt; funded by cable lobby group Broadband for America regarding the millions of comments submitted to the FCC’s public docket surrounding the agency’s plan to gut Title II net neutrality rules that prevent companies like AT&amp;amp;T and Verizon from charging extra fees, throttling apps and services, and censoring online content.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The most telling statistic in the report is that the unique comments in the docket &amp;ndash; the ones that people took the extra time to write themselves &amp;ndash; are overwhelmingly in favor of Title II net neutrality protections, by more than 73 to 1. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;152&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;750&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://78.media.tumblr.com/1a358f0e4292d6d7cc8ecb151144bf5b/tumblr_inline_ovi9hz2vks1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;152&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;750&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;So the telecom industry’s &lt;b&gt;own study&lt;/b&gt; essentially shows what nearly &lt;a href=&quot;http://thehill.com/policy/technology/341850-poll-gop-voters-support-net-neutrality-rules-oppose-att-time-warner-merger&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;all&lt;/a&gt; other &lt;a href=&quot;http://thehill.com/policy/technology/339137-poll-60-percent-of-voters-support-fccs-net-neutrality-rules&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;polling&lt;/a&gt; on this issue &lt;a href=&quot;https://morningconsult.com/2017/06/21/poll-shows-broad-bipartisan-support-net-neutrality-rules/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;has shown&lt;/a&gt;: that they are getting trounced when it comes to public opinion, and people from across the political spectrum overwhelmingly agree that they don’t want their ISPs to have control over what they can see and do on the Internet. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The report also highlights that the data in the FCC docket is a mess. Fight for the Future has been working with a group of tech volunteers to analyze this data as well, and will be releasing our findings soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Much of the reporting on this study draws a false equivalence between real comments from real people gathered through grassroots activism campaigns with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-13-update-historic-day-of-action-for-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;massive&lt;/a&gt; public participation &amp;ndash; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.comcastroturf.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;completely fraudulent comments&lt;/a&gt; that use names and addresses from breached databases, or completely fake information. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sadly, this confusion appears to be by design. Under Ajit Pai’s leadership, the FCC has repeatedly refused to address serious cybersecurity and transparency issues surrounding their public comment process, from the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-08-07-breaking-former-fcc-security-employee-destroys/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;now debunked&lt;/a&gt; claims of DDoS attacks to the confirmed fraudulent comments that the agency won’t remove from its docket. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The agency is sabotaging the legitimacy of its own proceeding in a cynical attempt to spread confusion about something that is actually as clear as day: the majority of the voices calling for the end of net neutrality protections are those bought and paid for by the industry that stands to gain unprecedented control of our online experience if they succeed in rigging the game and gutting these consumer protections at the FCC or through bad legislation billed as a “compromise.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 11:44:41 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-08-30-cable-industrys-own-study-shows-their-plan-to/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-08-30-cable-industrys-own-study-shows-their-plan-to/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Net neutrality advocates release more crowdfunded billboards exposing key lawmakers who are supporting the FCC’s net neutrality repeal</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;3456&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;4608&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://78.media.tumblr.com/bc4946c40d136e17ab4533eed55b1db0/tumblr_inline_ovgfv2Pgo71ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;3456&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;4608&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, August 29, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, press@fightforthefuture.org, 978-852-6457&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;New billboards in three states single out members of Congress who support the FCC’s plan to gut rules stopping ISPs from charging new fees, slowing traffic, or blocking websites&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today digital rights organization Fight for the Future unveiled 3 more crowdfunded billboards targeting Representatives &lt;b&gt;Cathy McMorris Rodgers&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt; Bob Latta,&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Greg Walden&lt;/b&gt;, members of Congress who have publicly supported the FCC’s efforts to gut net neutrality protections that keep the web free from censorship, throttling, and extra fees. The three new billboards are the latest in an ongoing campaign focused on lawmakers who oppose Internet freedom. Earlier this month the group launched an initial&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2017/08/pro-net-neutrality-billboards-shame-lawmakers-who-want-to-repeal-rules/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;round of net neutrality&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;billboards&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; targeting six different lawmakers in states across the country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The move comes just hours before the FCC’s&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2017/8/11/16135708/fcc-net-neutrality-comment-period-extended-two-weeks&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;final deadline for public input&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;on their controversial plan to repeal net neutrality. With lawmakers still in their home districts, the billboards -&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://donate.fightforthefuture.org/campaigns/nnbillboards/#page-1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;paid for&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;by hundreds of small donations - appear in three different states.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See PHOTOS of the 3 new billboards here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/a/UHfXJ&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://imgur.com/a/UHfXJ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since the massive July 12th day of action, millions have contacted their representatives – who have oversight over the FCC – to ensure these key protections are not changed or removed. The billboards send a strong message to any Members of Congress contemplating support for the FCC’s plan to repeal net neutrality, which is currently being tracked through a &lt;b&gt;“&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.battleforthenet.com/#scoreboard&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;congressional scorecard&lt;/a&gt;” &lt;/b&gt;on BattleForTheNet.com. So far very few lawmakers have been willing to publicly support Ajit Pai’s plan, likely in light of polling that shows voters &amp;ndash; including Republicans &amp;ndash; overwhelmingly oppose it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;411&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;643&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://78.media.tumblr.com/ad389d5c048d96ca1756cd5c7ed6f993/tumblr_inline_ovgfv7AHwI1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;411&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;643&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The billboards encourage constituents to contact their elected representatives; for example, Committee on Energy and Commerce Chairman Rep. Greg Walden’s (R-OR) billboard in Medford, Oregon asks, “Want slower, more expensive Internet? Rep. Walden supports CenturyLink’s plan to destroy net neutrality. Ask him why: (541) 776-4646.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The outdoor ads feature some of the few members of Congress who came out with early support for FCC’s plan to repeal net neutrality rules, including:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Spokane, WA &lt;/b&gt;– Rep. Cathy McMorris Rodgers (N. Monroe Street at W. Broadway Ave)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Findlay, OH &lt;/b&gt;– Rep. Bob Latta (corner of E Main Cross St and East St.)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Medford, OR&lt;/b&gt; – Rep. Greg Walden (N. Pacific Hwy at Elm Ave)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It doesn’t matter which party you’re in, or how charming you are on TV &amp;ndash; if you attack net neutrality and Internet freedom we will make sure everyone knows that you’re corrupt to the core” &lt;b&gt;said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future (pronouns: she/hers), &lt;/b&gt;“every member of Congress should take note: supporting the FCC’s plan to allow censorship, throttling, and price gouging may get you a few extra campaign donations from big telecom companies, but it will infuriate your constituents, and will come with a serious political cost.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The billboards highlight the increasing scrutiny on Congress - who have important oversight authority over the FCC. With no viable legislation on the table, net neutrality supporters remain opposed to any attempt at legislation that would undermine the strong rules at the FCC, which were fought for by millions of Americans, and are calling on lawmakers to publicly oppose Ajit Pai’s plan, and require the FCC to act with transparency and address &lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/163913891863/breaking-former-fcc-security-employee-destroys&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;serious irregularities&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; in its rulemaking process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future was also one of the leading organizations behind the historic Internet-Wide Day of Action for Net Neutrality on July 12,&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.fightforthefuture.org%2Fnews%2F2017-07-13-update-historic-day-of-action-for-net-neutrality%2F&amp;amp;t=YmFhMmU0MGQ2YWEzMTJmMDcxYzRlYjJjMGRmNjE0YzgxODhmOTcwNCx2cnltU0FjZQ%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F163913891863%2Fbreaking-former-fcc-security-employee-destroys&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;which drove&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; a record breaking 2 million+ comments to the FCC and Congress in a single day. Learn more at &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Ffightforthefuture.org&amp;amp;t=NDc0NWJkZWMwYTkyY2UyZDNmN2FhOTU0MjI3NGUzYzk0NDMxZjNlNix2cnltU0FjZQ%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F163913891863%2Fbreaking-former-fcc-security-employee-destroys&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;554&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;730&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://78.media.tumblr.com/ba97e7010820a4d2ac5f8fa361f54708/tumblr_inline_ovgfvjOMkb1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;554&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;730&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 12:16:59 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-08-29-net-neutrality-advocates-release-more-crowdfunded/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-08-29-net-neutrality-advocates-release-more-crowdfunded/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Net neutrality activists launch crowdfunded billboards targeting key members of Congress during August recess</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;728&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;400&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://78.media.tumblr.com/1bd85ccb097a41ccbe5990b397f2781e/tumblr_inline_ouq674OTlq1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;728&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;400&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, August 15, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Tiffiniy Cheng, 413-367-6255, press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Billboards in six states single out lawmakers who support the FCC’s plan to gut key safeguards preventing ISPs from charging new fees, slowing traffic, or blocking websites&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today digital rights organization Fight for the Future unleashed a series of crowdfunded billboards targeting lawmakers who support FCC Chairman Ajit Pai’s efforts to repeal the country’s net neutrality rules. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With members of Congress back in their home districts, the billboards -&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://donate.fightforthefuture.org/campaigns/nnbillboards/#page-1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;paid for&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;by hundreds of small donations - appear in six different states just weeks before the FCC’s final deadline for public input on their proposal to gut net neutrality rules that prevent companies like Comcast, Verizon, and AT&amp;amp;T from charging extra fees, throttling, or blocking websites, apps, and online services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See PHOTOS of some of the billboards here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/a/lhEko&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://imgur.com/a/lhEko&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since the massive July 12th day of action, millions have contacted their representatives – who have oversight over the FCC – to ensure these key protections are not changed or removed. The billboards send a strong message to any Members of Congress contemplating support for the FCC’s plan to repeal net neutrality, which is currently being tracked through a &lt;b&gt;“&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.battleforthenet.com/#scoreboard&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;congressional scorecard&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;” on BattleForTheNet.com. So far very few lawmakers have been willing to publicly support Ajit Pai’s plan, likely in light of polling that shows voters &amp;ndash; including Republicans &amp;ndash; overwhelmingly oppose it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;3073&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1417&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://78.media.tumblr.com/43709916731ba6fa49023c4087876433/tumblr_inline_ouq6amcwc61ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;3073&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1417&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The billboards encourage constituents to contact their elected representatives; for example, Speaker Paul Ryan’s billboard in Janesville, WI asks, “Want slower, more expensive Internet? Rep. Paul Ryan supports Charter’s plan to destroy net neutrality. Ask him why: (608) 752-4050.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The outdoor ads feature some of the few members of Congress who came out with early support for FCC’s plan to repeal net neutrality rules, including:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clarksville, TN – Rep. Marsha Blackburn (Sources: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2017/05/31/blackburn-fccs-rollback-net-neutrality-rules-a-positive-step/356558001/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;USA Today&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://energycommerce.house.gov/news-center/press-releases/bicameral-leaders-comment-pai-s-internet-regulations-announcement&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Energy and Commerce Committee media release&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2017/01/enemy-of-net-neutrality-and-muni-broadband-will-chair-house-telecom-panel/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Ars Technica&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dalton, GA – Rep. Tom Graves (Sources: &lt;a href=&quot;https://act.represent.us/sign/Net_neutrality_contributions/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Represent.us&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://tomgraves.house.gov/newsroom/documentsingle.aspx?DocumentID=398756&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;media release&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/RepTomGraves/status/857349425538248704&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bakersfield, CA – Rep. Kevin McCarthy (Sources: &lt;a href=&quot;http://thehill.com/policy/technology/341867-house-republican-leadership-cautions-tech-on-net-neutrality-report&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Hill&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.axios.com/republicans-nudge-big-tech-over-net-neutrality-activism-2458262562.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Axios&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/2014/06/20/new-house-majority-leader-opposes-net-neutrality-just-like-his-predecessor/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;TechCrunch&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Janesville, WI– Rep. Paul Ryan (Sources: &lt;a href=&quot;http://thehill.com/policy/technology/330754-ryan-cheers-fcc-chiefs-plans-to-roll-back-net-neutrality&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Hill&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;http://thehill.com/policy/technology/341867-house-republican-leadership-cautions-tech-on-net-neutrality-report&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Hill&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rapid City, SD – Sen. John Thune (Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://energycommerce.house.gov/news-center/press-releases/bicameral-leaders-comment-pai-s-internet-regulations-announcement&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Energy and Commerce Committee media release&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Jackson, MS – Sen. Roger Wicker (Sources: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.incompas.org/files/IMGEInsights-Presentations-KeyFindings-1c.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;INCOMPAS poll&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.mozilla.org/blog/2017/06/06/new-mozilla-poll-americans-political-parties-overwhelmingly-support-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Mozilla poll&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&quot;https://energycommerce.house.gov/news-center/press-releases/bicameral-leaders-comment-pai-s-internet-regulations-announcement&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;media release&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Politicians need to learn that they can’t attack free speech on the Internet and expect to get away with it,” &lt;b&gt;said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future (pronouns: she/hers), &lt;/b&gt;“Voters from across the political spectrum all agree that they don’t want companies like Comcast and Verizon dictating what they can see and do online. No one is fooled by corrupt lawmakers’ attempts to push for bad legislation while they strip Internet users of protections at the FCC. Hundreds of people donated to make these billboards possible. When you come for the Internet, the Internet comes for you.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;2851&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1467&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://78.media.tumblr.com/ce131a0c2be5f848ec6054900d0cc6c5/tumblr_inline_ouq6dcuGgv1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;2851&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1467&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The billboards highlight the increasing scrutiny on Congress - who have important oversight authority over the FCC. With no viable legislation on the table, net neutrality supporters remain opposed to any attempt at legislation that would undermine the strong rules at the FCC, which were fought for by millions of Americans, and are calling on lawmakers to publicly oppose Ajit Pai’s plan, and require the FCC to act with transparency and address &lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/163913891863/breaking-former-fcc-security-employee-destroys&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;serious &lt;b&gt;irregularities&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;in its rulemaking process. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future was also one of the leading organizations behind the historic Internet-Wide Day of Action for Net Neutrality on July 12, &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.fightforthefuture.org%2Fnews%2F2017-07-13-update-historic-day-of-action-for-net-neutrality%2F&amp;amp;t=YmFhMmU0MGQ2YWEzMTJmMDcxYzRlYjJjMGRmNjE0YzgxODhmOTcwNCx2cnltU0FjZQ%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F163913891863%2Fbreaking-former-fcc-security-employee-destroys&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;which drove&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; a record breaking 2 million+ comments to the FCC and Congress in a single day. Learn more at&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Ffightforthefuture.org&amp;amp;t=NDc0NWJkZWMwYTkyY2UyZDNmN2FhOTU0MjI3NGUzYzk0NDMxZjNlNix2cnltU0FjZQ%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F163913891863%2Fbreaking-former-fcc-security-employee-destroys&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;571&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;856&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://78.media.tumblr.com/eb00a4a7e8d8476ad087da9da007d450/tumblr_inline_ouq6e45MqU1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;571&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;856&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;SOURCES FOR BILLBOARDS:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where do the featured lawmakers stand?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rep. Marsha Blackburn: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2017/05/31/blackburn-fccs-rollback-net-neutrality-rules-a-positive-step/356558001/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;USA Today&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://energycommerce.house.gov/news-center/press-releases/bicameral-leaders-comment-pai-s-internet-regulations-announcement&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Energy and Commerce Committee press release&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2017/01/enemy-of-net-neutrality-and-muni-broadband-will-chair-house-telecom-panel/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Ars Technica&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rep. Tom Graves: &lt;a href=&quot;https://act.represent.us/sign/Net_neutrality_contributions/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Represent.us&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://tomgraves.house.gov/newsroom/documentsingle.aspx?DocumentID=398756&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Rep. Graves&amp;rsquo; press release&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/RepTomGraves/status/857349425538248704&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;@RepTomGraves tweet&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rep. Kevin McCarthy: &lt;a href=&quot;http://thehill.com/policy/technology/341867-house-republican-leadership-cautions-tech-on-net-neutrality-report&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Hill&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.axios.com/republicans-nudge-big-tech-over-net-neutrality-activism-2458262562.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Axios&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/2014/06/20/new-house-majority-leader-opposes-net-neutrality-just-like-his-predecessor/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;TechCrunch&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rep. Paul Ryan: &lt;a href=&quot;http://thehill.com/policy/technology/330754-ryan-cheers-fcc-chiefs-plans-to-roll-back-net-neutrality&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Hill&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;http://thehill.com/policy/technology/341867-house-republican-leadership-cautions-tech-on-net-neutrality-report&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Hill&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sen. John Thune: &lt;a href=&quot;https://energycommerce.house.gov/news-center/press-releases/bicameral-leaders-comment-pai-s-internet-regulations-announcement&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Energy and Commerce Committee press release&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sen. Roger Wicker: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.incompas.org/files/IMGEInsights-Presentations-KeyFindings-1c.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;INCOMPAS poll&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.mozilla.org/blog/2017/06/06/new-mozilla-poll-americans-political-parties-overwhelmingly-support-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Mozilla poll&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&quot;https://energycommerce.house.gov/news-center/press-releases/bicameral-leaders-comment-pai-s-internet-regulations-announcement&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Energy and Commerce Committee press release&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;What is at stake if we lose strong net neutrality rules? &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;“Under the current net neutrality rules, broadband providers like Comcast and Charter, and wireless providers like AT&amp;amp;T and Verizon, can&amp;rsquo;t block or slow down your access to lawful content, nor can they create so-called &amp;ldquo;fast lanes&amp;rdquo; for content providers who are willing to pay extra.”&lt;/i&gt;  Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wired.com/story/why-net-neutrality-matters-even-in-the-age-of-oligopoly/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;WIRED&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;‘In dispute are a set of U.S. federal regulations saying that internet providers should not slow down, block or charge websites extra fees while treating other sites differently. The Federal Communications Commission is currently weighing how to repeal those so-called “net neutrality” rules, in a move that’s expected to benefit internet providers such as Verizon and AT&amp;amp;T.’&lt;/i&gt; Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/the-switch/wp/2017/07/11/your-favorite-websites-might-look-a-little-different-soon-heres-why/?utm_term=.c90e573ee862&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Washington Post&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 09:51:42 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-08-15-net-neutrality-activists-launch-crowdfunded/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-08-15-net-neutrality-activists-launch-crowdfunded/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BREAKING: former FCC security employee destroys agency’s claims of DDoS attacks following John Oliver net neutrality segments</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;614&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;560&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://78.media.tumblr.com/f1a5ba1c8a2fd74f00929b22c3c46896/tumblr_inline_oubvczLsoL1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;614&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;560&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, August 7, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;, 978-852-6457&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Bombshell story from Gizmodo underscores need for FCC to address serious issues with its public comment process before making any decision on net neutrality. 15,000+ people call on lawmakers to demand that FCC comply with transparency laws&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a &lt;a href=&quot;http://gizmodo.com/senior-us-official-claimed-the-fcc-got-hacked-after-sec-1797593781&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;bombshell story&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; from Gizmodo today, a former FCC security employee lays waste to the agency’s claims that a pair of &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-20-fcc-now-says-it-has-no-documentation-of-ddos/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DDoS attacks&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;took down the FCC comment website at the exact moments when large amounts of pro net neutrality comments would have been flooding into the docket following viral segments from comedian John Oliver in 2014 and 2017. The agency’s inability to maintain a functional way for the public to comment on its net neutrality proceedings has become an issue of concern for members of Congress overseeing the agency, and raises questions about how it can or should move forward with its rulemaking process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The security expert who spoke to Gizmodo reveals that the FCC security team concluded that there had not been a malicious attack after the John Oliver segment in 2014. But until-recent FCC CIO David Bray told reporters that anyway, despite the fact there was no evidence of it, and he did not even have access to the types of logs and information that could have led him to that conclusion. The source also leaked a photo of the FCC’s server room to Gizmodo, revealing a mess of wires that would make any competent IT professional cringe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When pressed, Bray admitted to being the source of news reports about the made up “hacking” attack, but he never reported the incident to the Department of Homeland Security, who require that government agencies notify them of such attacks. With the backing of the FCC press office, Bray fed reporters that exact same story when the agency’s comment system collapsed again this year, preventing large numbers of people from making their voices heard in the agency’s proceeding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future, said:&lt;/b&gt; “These latest revelations are outrageous. A senior FCC official intentionally misled the public and invented cyber attacks to cover up the fact that the agency is failing at their responsibility to maintain a functioning system to receive feedback about an issue that affects every single person using the Internet. The FCC must address these serious issues with their comment process before moving forward, or it will be clear that this is a rogue agency that answers only to large telecom companies, and not to the American people.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The news comes after more than 15,000 people signed &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://actionnetwork.org/petitions/tell-congress-demand-that-the-fcc-comply-with-transparency-laws&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;a petition&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;calling on their lawmakers to instruct the FCC to comply with transparency laws as the agency moves ahead with its unpopular plan to gut net neutrality protections that prevent ISPs from charging extra fees, throttling, or blocking content online. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The agency is currently facing multiple lawsuits for refusing to release information related to the now-debunked DDoS claims, Chairman Ajit Pai’s discussions with telecom companies,  large amounts of &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-06-12-more-than-15000-people-call-on-the-fcc-to-remove/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;fake comments&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;using real people’s names and addresses without their permission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Members of Congress need to understand that this is not an issue they can ignore or hide from,” &lt;b&gt;Greer added,&lt;/b&gt; “Voters from across the political spectrum overwhelmingly support the current net neutrality rules, and want their Senators and Representatives to do their job and speak out to ensure that the FCC is listening to the will of the public, not just to lobbyists from giant telecom companies. Lawmakers from both sides of the aisle need to exercise their oversight and demand that the FCC act transparently during this proceeding.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future has been working to inform the public about the serious issues surrounding the FCC’s comment process. The group organized &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-05-25-letter-to-the-fcc-from-people-whose-names-and/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;a letter&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;from dozens of people whose names and addresses were used to submit anti net neutrality comments without their permission, as well as several petitions garnering tens of thousands of signatures calling on the agency to come clean about the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-20-fcc-now-says-it-has-no-documentation-of-ddos/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;alleged DDoS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;attack that prevented concerned citizens from submitting comments. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future was also one of the leading organizations behind the historic Internet-Wide Day of Action for Net Neutrality on July 12, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-13-update-historic-day-of-action-for-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;which drove&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; a record breaking 2 million+ comments to the FCC and Congress in a single day. Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;http://fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;fightforthefuture.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 14:29:29 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-08-07-breaking-former-fcc-security-employee-destroys/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-08-07-breaking-former-fcc-security-employee-destroys/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FCC now says it has no documentation of DDoS attack it claims took down website following John Oliver net neutrality segment</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;466&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;700&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://78.media.tumblr.com/8bf2e585ae4cb043d128564aee667f18/tumblr_inline_ote94cKHc21ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;466&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;700&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, July 20, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;, 978-852-6457&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Agency refuses to release hundreds of pages of documents related to alleged incident. Congress must demand answers.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Federal Communications Commission (FCC) &lt;a href=&quot;http://gizmodo.com/fcc-now-says-there-is-no-documented-analysis-of-the-cyb-1797073113&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;admitted&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; last night that it has no “documented analysis” to back up its claim that a DDoS attack took down the agency’s public comment website immediately following a viral John Oliver segment about net neutrality in May. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The news comes in response to a Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) request from Gizmodo &amp;ndash; but the FCC &lt;a href=&quot;http://gizmodo.com/fcc-now-says-there-is-no-documented-analysis-of-the-cyb-1797073113&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;refused&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to release more than 200 pages of additional documents related to the alleged incident. Fight for the Future, a  nonpartisan digital rights organization that played a lead role in the massive net neutrality day of action on July 12, issued the following statement, which can be attributed to campaign director Evan Greer (pronouns: she/her):&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;“At this point even supporters of Ajit Pai’s plan to gut online free speech protections have to be wondering: what is the FCC hiding? &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This federal agency has a responsibility to maintain a functioning website for the public to comment on proceedings that have a profound impact on our economy, our democracy, and the future of the Internet. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;It’s clear that the FCC has failed to perform this basic duty, and now they are refusing to release hundreds of pages of documents that could help shed light on what really happened here, and who, if anyone, has been attempting to interfere with the public comment process.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;The public deserves to know whether former Verizon lawyer Ajit Pai is protecting the person or organization behind these alleged DDoS attacks and the flood of fake comments using stolen identities that have tainted the FCC’s docket. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Net neutrality protections protect Internet users from extra fees, censorship, and throttling. Members of Congress who oversee the FCC must demand that the agency provide adequate answers to these serious questions surrounding their comment process before they make any decision about net neutrality rules that affect hundreds of millions of Internet users.” &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future is one of the leading grassroots organizations fighting for net neutrality and Internet freedom. The group recently &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-18-net-neutrality-activists-set-sights-on-congress/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;plans to crowdfund billboards to expose members of Congress who support the FCC’s plan to dismantle net neutrality protections, and launched a scorecard to make it easy for voters to learn where their lawmakers stand on the issue. The group also played a lead role in the massive July 12 day of action &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-13-update-historic-day-of-action-for-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;that drove&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;millions of comments, emails, and phone calls to decision makers in support of the Title II rules. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 10:48:16 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-20-fcc-now-says-it-has-no-documentation-of-ddos/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-20-fcc-now-says-it-has-no-documentation-of-ddos/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fight for the Future statement in response to White House comments on FCC plan to dismantle net neutrality free speech protections</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, July 18, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;News reports today indicate that the White House has offered comments regarding the FCC’s plan to slash Title II based net neutrality protections that prevent companies like Comcast and AT&amp;amp;T from charging extra fees, or engaging in throttling, offering paid fast lanes, and censorship. Digital rights group Fight for the Future, a leading net neutrality organization that played a key role in the recent massive day of action on July 12, issued the following statement, which can be attributed to campaign director, Evan Greer (pronouns: she/her):&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;“The White House’s comments today are far from full throated support for the FCC’s plan, and underscore the reality that voters from across the political spectrum, including &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.newsmax.com/Newsfront/internet-free-and-open-service-providers-conservatives/2017/07/13/id/801539/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;more than 75%&lt;/a&gt; of those who voted for Donald Trump, support strong net neutrality protections that keep the web free of extra fees, throttling, and censorship. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;FCC chairman Ajit Pai is increasingly isolated &amp;ndash; he has clearly misjudged the Republican base. No one wants companies like Comcast, Verizon, and AT&amp;amp;T to have the power to decide what we can see and what we can say on the Internet.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;The White House fell far short of supporting the FCC’s plan, and only noted that they are right to “review” the current rules. This is a clear signal that they know how unpopular the repeal of net neutrality rules is with voters, including conservatives and libertarians.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Net neutrality is the free speech fight of our generation. Internet users are outraged and paying attention. Decision makers in Washington, DC need to listen to the public, not just lobbyists from big telecom companies. When they do, they’ll realize that allowing the FCC to move forward with their plan to slash net neutrality protections will result in them being seen by constituents as enemies of the Internet, enemies of innovation, and enemies of freedom.”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-18-net-neutrality-activists-set-sights-on-congress/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;announced &lt;/a&gt;this morning plans to turn its focus to Congress, with a new wave of billboards focused on lawmakers who support the FCC’s plan, and a “congressional scorecard” to make it easy for voters to learn where their members stand. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Background on the historic July 12 net neutrality day of action: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nearly all of the most popular websites on the web participated in a historic Internet-Wide &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com/july12&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Day of Action&lt;/a&gt; to Save Net Neutrality on July 12, 2017 to oppose the FCC’s plan to slash Title II, the legal foundation for net neutrality rules that protect online free speech and innovation. A flood of web platforms small and large like Twitter, Reddit, Netflix, Spotify, 4chan, Airbnb, Amazon, Mozilla, OK Cupid, Vimeo, Tinder, Expedia, Pornhub, Imgur, Yelp, Spotify, and Soundcloud &amp;ndash; along with a vast array of online communities from every corner of the Internet: gaming forums, YouTube creators, subreddits and more &amp;ndash; displayed prominent protest messages to their users, encouraging them to take action by contacting the FCC and Congress through tools like &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;BattleForTheNet.com&lt;/a&gt; that make it easy for Internet users to make their voices heard. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See PHOTOS, IMAGES, and DESCRIPTIONS of how participants are protesting here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/vYVet&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://imgur.com/a/vYVet&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;SEE A SAMPLING OF VIDEO COMMENTS here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/225341994/852009671a&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://vimeo.com/225341994/852009671a&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was so much activity on this day that organizers are still in the process of documenting and compiling it, but here are some initial numbers showing the scale of this massive event:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tens of millions of people saw the protest messages on participating websites&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Over 5 million emails to Congress (which will be delivered over coming days)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;More than 2 million comments to the FCC (nearly tripling our Sept. 10th 2014 “Internet Slowdown” record for most in a single day)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;More than 125,000 phone calls to Congress&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;#NetNeutrality trended on both Facebook and Twitter&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Protesters went in person to more than 20 Congressional offices &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;More than 125,000 websites, people, artists, online creators, and organizations signed up to participate in the initial call to protest&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Celebrities flocked to support the effort including &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/PearlJam/status/885230542576205824&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pearl Jam&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Wilco/status/885233478719221762&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Wilco&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/PearlJam/status/885230542576205824&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Wil Wheaton&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/TimRobbins1/status/885154464432136192&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tim Robbins&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/SusanSarandon/status/885196657792516097&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Susan Sarandon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/blues_traveler/status/885242752656605184&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Blues Traveler&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/stephenfry/status/884942083252920320&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Steven Fry&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/MarkRuffalo/status/885098668910444544&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Mark Ruffalo&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/LauraJaneGrace/status/885226732369960964&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Laura Jane Grace&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/kendrick38/status/885159414902042628&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Kendrick Sampson&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://consequenceofsound.net/2017/07/ted-leo-and-amanda-palmer-explain-why-we-need-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Amanda Palmer&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://consequenceofsound.net/2017/07/ted-leo-and-amanda-palmer-explain-why-we-need-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Ted Leo&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/FullFrontalSamB/status/885257665924018176&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Samantha Bee&lt;/a&gt;, and many more.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Broad participation from every corner of the Internet: from online gaming communities to librarians to real estate sites to grassroots organizations to independent musicians. &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/vYVet&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;See a gallery here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Facebook, Google, and Dropbox three of the largest Internet companies, came out publicly with strong statements in support of the current FCC rules. This is significant &amp;ndash; especially given Facebook’s previous opposition to certain net neutrality rules, notably in India.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The effort is led by many of the grassroots groups behind the largest online protests in history including the SOPA blackout and the &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com/infographic&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Internet Slowdown&lt;/a&gt;. Media attention for online mobilizations tends to focus on the big names participating, but there is a much more interesting story: a coalition of Internet activists huddled over their laptops in coworking spaces, home offices, and coffee shops, who are the ones who came up with the idea, called for, and organized the protest, and have since been working together to lay the groundwork, build the technical tools, and create the educational resources that make it possible for large and small websites to participate in these mass days of action. It’s a grassroots effort involving dozens of volunteers working together in Slack channels, outreach spreadsheets, endless email chains, organizing in online communities and forums, and an enormous amount of creativity and digital elbow grease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The list of sites and apps participating has grown so quickly it’s almost impossible to keep up, but participants include Automattic (Wordpress), eBay, Rosetta Stone, Pinterest, Amazon, Mozilla, Netflix, Etsy, Kickstarter, Soundcloud, Dropbox, Spotify, Redfin, Facebook, Google, Snapchat, Medium, Y Combinator, GitHub, Pantheon, Opera, Bittorrent Inc., Shapeways, Nextdoor, Stack Overflow, Funny Or Die, Dreamhost, and CREDO Mobile, Goldenfrog, Fark, Chess.com, Namecheap, DuckDuckGo, Checkout.com, Sonic, Ting, ProtonMail, O’Reilly Media, SlashDot, Dribble, Dischord, SourceForge, and Union Square Ventures. Organizations participating include Fight for the Future, Free Press Action Fund, Demand Progress, Center for Media Justice, EFF,  Internet Association, Internet Archive, World Wide Web Foundation, Creative Commons, National Hispanic Media Coalition, Greenpeace, Common Cause, ACLU, Rock the Vote, American Library Association, Daily Kos, OpenMedia, The Nation, PCCC, MoveOn, OFA, Public Knowledge, OTI, Color of Change, MoveOn, Free Software Foundation, Internet Creators Guild, the Women’s March, and many others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 16:59:39 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-18-fight-for-the-future-statement-in-response-to/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-18-fight-for-the-future-statement-in-response-to/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fight for the Future Statement Regarding Incorrect Billboard Report</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, July 18, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This morning Fight for the Future &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-18-net-neutrality-activists-set-sights-on-congress/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;plans to put up crowdfunded billboards focused on members of Congress who oppose net neutrality protections.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rep Scalise’s name was incorrectly included in private emails to two reporters, due to a copy paste error, and reported by Politico. This error was immediately corrected once brought to our attention, and we regret the confusion it caused. We would obviously not run billboards against someone who is in the hospital, and wish Rep Scalise a speedy recovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As for the billboards focused on other members, Congress plays an important role overseeing the FCC, and voters deserve to know where their members stand. The goal of our billboards is to make sure that the public knows which members are supporting the FCC’s plan to dismantle important net neutrality protections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 15:26:35 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-18-fight-for-the-future-statement-regarding-incorrect/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-18-fight-for-the-future-statement-regarding-incorrect/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Net Neutrality activists set sights on Congress: plan to unleash new wave of billboards and scorecard for lawmakers following historic day of action</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2536&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;3944&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://78.media.tumblr.com/d1e644ec92f4901d0f4bb5bd3488fd6d/tumblr_inline_otaelbVFXH1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2536&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;3944&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, July 18, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;July 12 protest drove record numbers of comments, emails, and phone calls&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Digital rights group Fight for the Future unveiled today the next steps in the battle for the future of the Internet: turning the focus on Congress &amp;ndash; who have oversight over the FCC and whose actions will determine whether Ajit Pai’s unpopular plan moves forward &amp;ndash; with a wave of &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://donate.fightforthefuture.org/campaigns/nnbillboards/#page-1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;crowdfunded billboards&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;and a &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.battleforthenet.com/#scoreboard&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;“congressional scorecard”&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;on BattleForTheNet.com showing where lawmakers stand. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group has already raised more than $50,000 toward the billboards, which will go up in the coming weeks targeting lawmakers who support FCC Chairman Ajit Pai’s plan to gut net neutrality rules that prevent companies like Comcast, AT&amp;amp;T, and Verizon from charging extra fees, slowing down websites, and engaging in censorship. The congressional scorecard makes it easy for voters to quickly learn their representative’s positions, and impossible for members of Congress to hide from their constituents. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See the crowdfunding page for the billboards here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://donate.fightforthefuture.org/campaigns/nnbillboards/#page-1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://donate.fightforthefuture.org/campaigns/nnbillboards/#page-1&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See the congressional scorecard here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.battleforthenet.com/#scoreboard&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.battleforthenet.com/#scoreboard&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Internet users are pissed off and paying attention,” &lt;b&gt;said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future, &lt;/b&gt;“Any lawmaker that stands idly by and allows the FCC to gut these basic free speech protections that people from across the political spectrum overwhelmingly support will be seen as an enemy of the Internet and an enemy of free speech. These billboards, and the scorecard, are just the beginning.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group plans to initially put up billboards targeting House GOP leadership members who used a meeting last week &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://thehill.com/policy/technology/341867-house-republican-leadership-cautions-tech-on-net-neutrality-report&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;to threaten&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;tech companies who were participating in the historic net neutrality day of action on July 12&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-13-update-historic-day-of-action-for-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;which drove&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;millions of comments, emails and phone calls to decision makers, and saw broad participation from every corner of the Internet from major web platforms, startups, YouTubers, gamers, and forums like 4chan and reddit. The billboards will also mention lawmakers vote to gut Internet privacy rules that prevent ISPs from collecting and selling customer information to advertisers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.battleforthenet.com/#scoreboard&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;congressional scorecard&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;divides Congress into two camps: Team Internet (those who are speaking up to defend net neutrality rules that protect online free speech) and Team Cable (those who are supporting the FCC’s plan to dismantle those protections and give Cable companies control over our online experience.) Lawmakers on “Team Cable” should expect to be targeted with billboards in the coming weeks if they do not speak out against Ajit Pai’s plan. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The announcements of both the billboards and scorecard come as all eyes shift to the Senate where Ajit Pai is expected to be confirmed as commissioner this week in a largely procedural vote. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Background on the historic July 12 net neutrality day of action: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nearly all of the most popular websites on the web participated in a historic Internet-Wide &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com/july12&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Day of Action&lt;/a&gt; to Save Net Neutrality on July 12, 2017 to oppose the FCC’s plan to slash Title II, the legal foundation for net neutrality rules that protect online free speech and innovation. A flood of web platforms small and large like Twitter, Reddit, Netflix, Spotify, 4chan, Airbnb, Amazon, Mozilla, OK Cupid, Vimeo, Tinder, Expedia, Pornhub, Imgur, Yelp, Spotify, and Soundcloud &amp;ndash; along with a vast array of online communities from every corner of the Internet: gaming forums, YouTube creators, subreddits and more &amp;ndash; displayed prominent protest messages to their users, encouraging them to take action by contacting the FCC and Congress through tools like &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;BattleForTheNet.com&lt;/a&gt; that make it easy for Internet users to make their voices heard. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See PHOTOS, IMAGES, and DESCRIPTIONS of how participants are protesting here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/vYVet&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://imgur.com/a/vYVet&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;SEE A SAMPLING OF VIDEO COMMENTS here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/225341994/852009671a&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://vimeo.com/225341994/852009671a&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was so much activity on this day that organizers are still in the process of documenting and compiling it, but here are some initial numbers showing the scale of this massive event:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tens of millions of people saw the protest messages on participating websites&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Over 5 million emails to Congress (which will be delivered over coming days)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;More than 2 million comments to the FCC (nearly tripling our Sept. 10th 2014 “Internet Slowdown” record for most in a single day)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;More than 125,000 phone calls to Congress&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;#NetNeutrality trended on both Facebook and Twitter&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Protesters went in person to more than 20 Congressional offices &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;More than 125,000 websites, people, artists, online creators, and organizations signed up to participate in the initial call to protest&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Celebrities flocked to support the effort including &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/PearlJam/status/885230542576205824&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pearl Jam&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Wilco/status/885233478719221762&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Wilco&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/PearlJam/status/885230542576205824&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Wil Wheaton&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/TimRobbins1/status/885154464432136192&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tim Robbins&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/SusanSarandon/status/885196657792516097&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Susan Sarandon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/blues_traveler/status/885242752656605184&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Blues Traveler&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/stephenfry/status/884942083252920320&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Steven Fry&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/MarkRuffalo/status/885098668910444544&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Mark Ruffalo&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/LauraJaneGrace/status/885226732369960964&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Laura Jane Grace&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/kendrick38/status/885159414902042628&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Kendrick Sampson&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://consequenceofsound.net/2017/07/ted-leo-and-amanda-palmer-explain-why-we-need-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Amanda Palmer&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://consequenceofsound.net/2017/07/ted-leo-and-amanda-palmer-explain-why-we-need-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Ted Leo&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/FullFrontalSamB/status/885257665924018176&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Samantha Bee&lt;/a&gt;, and many more.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Broad participation from every corner of the Internet: from online gaming communities to librarians to real estate sites to grassroots organizations to independent musicians. &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/vYVet&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;See a gallery here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Facebook, Google, and Dropbox three of the largest Internet companies, came out publicly with strong statements in support of the current FCC rules. This is significant &amp;ndash; especially given Facebook’s previous opposition to certain net neutrality rules, notably in India.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The effort is led by many of the grassroots groups behind the largest online protests in history including the SOPA blackout and the&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com/infographic&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Internet Slowdown&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/b&gt;Media attention for online mobilizations tends to focus on the big names participating, but there is a much more interesting story: a coalition of Internet activists huddled over their laptops in coworking spaces, home offices, and coffee shops, who are the ones who came up with the idea, called for, and organized the protest, and have since been working together to lay the groundwork, build the technical tools, and create the educational resources that make it possible for large and small websites to participate in these mass days of action. It’s a grassroots effort involving dozens of volunteers working together in Slack channels, outreach spreadsheets, endless email chains, organizing in online communities and forums, and an enormous amount of creativity and digital elbow grease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The list of sites and apps participating has grown so quickly it’s almost impossible to keep up, but participants include Automattic (Wordpress), eBay, Rosetta Stone, Pinterest, Amazon, Mozilla, Netflix, Etsy, Kickstarter, Soundcloud, Dropbox, Spotify, Redfin, Facebook, Google, Snapchat, Medium, Y Combinator, GitHub, Pantheon, Opera, Bittorrent Inc., Shapeways, Nextdoor, Stack Overflow, Funny Or Die, Dreamhost, and CREDO Mobile, Goldenfrog, Fark, Chess.com, Namecheap, DuckDuckGo, Checkout.com, Sonic, Ting, ProtonMail, O’Reilly Media, SlashDot, Dribble, Dischord, SourceForge, and Union Square Ventures. Organizations participating include Fight for the Future, Free Press Action Fund, Demand Progress, Center for Media Justice, EFF,  Internet Association, Internet Archive, World Wide Web Foundation, Creative Commons, National Hispanic Media Coalition, Greenpeace, Common Cause, ACLU, Rock the Vote, American Library Association, Daily Kos, OpenMedia, The Nation, PCCC, MoveOn, OFA, Public Knowledge, OTI, Color of Change, MoveOn, Free Software Foundation, Internet Creators Guild, the Women’s March, and many others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 08:57:56 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-18-net-neutrality-activists-set-sights-on-congress/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-18-net-neutrality-activists-set-sights-on-congress/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UPDATE: Historic day of action for Net Neutrality breaks records: more than 2 million comments to FCC, millions of emails and phone calls to Congress</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;vimeo&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fvimeo.com%2F225341994%2F852009671a&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/225341994?title=0&amp;amp;byline=0&amp;amp;portrait=0&quot; width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, July 13, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;More than 125,000 websites, Internet users, and organizations participated in a massive online protest against the FCC’s plan to gut protections that keep the web free from censorship, throttling, and extra fees. Protesters gathered in DC and showed up at Congressional district offices, celebs weigh in&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nearly all of the most popular websites on the web participated in a historic Internet-Wide &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com/july12&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Day of Action&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to Save Net Neutrality yesterday to oppose the FCC’s plan to slash Title II, the legal foundation for net neutrality rules that protect online free speech and innovation. A flood of web platforms small and large like Twitter, Reddit, Netflix, Spotify, 4chan, Airbnb, Amazon, Mozilla, OK Cupid, Vimeo, Tinder, Expedia, Pornhub, Imgur, Yelp, Spotify, and Soundcloud &amp;ndash; along with a vast array of online communities from every corner of the Internet: gaming forums, YouTube creators, subreddits and more &amp;ndash; displayed prominent protest messages to their users, encouraging them to take action by contacting the FCC and Congress through tools like &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;BattleForTheNet.com&lt;/a&gt; that make it easy for Internet users to make their voices heard. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See PHOTOS, IMAGES, and DESCRIPTIONS of how participants are protesting here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/vYVet&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://imgur.com/a/vYVet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;SEE A SAMPLING OF VIDEO COMMENTS here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/225341994/852009671a&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://vimeo.com/225341994/852009671a&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There has been such a surge in activity &amp;ndash; and the traffic is STILL coming in &amp;ndash; that organizers are still scrambling to document everything that has happened but so far through the BattleForTheNet.com site alone (not including the Internet Association’s page or other aligned efforts) we’ve seen:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;IMPORTANT NOTE: these numbers STILL represent only a portion of the final totals, and due to the massive numbers, comments and emails will be delivered over several days.  We will release additional updates as we continue documenting what has happened:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tens of millions of people saw the protest messages on participating websites&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Over 5 million emails to Congress &lt;/b&gt;(which will be delivered over coming days)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;More than 2 million comments to the FCC&lt;/b&gt; (nearly tripling our Sept. 10th 2014 “Internet Slowdown” record for most in a single day)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;124,000 phone calls to Congress&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;#NetNeutrality trended on both Facebook and Twitter&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Protesters &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/Zkop6&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;went in person&lt;/a&gt; to more than 20 Congressional offices &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;More than 125,000 websites, people, artists, online creators, and organizations&lt;/b&gt; signed up to participate in the initial call to protest&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Celebrities flocked to support the effort &lt;/b&gt;including &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/PearlJam/status/885230542576205824&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pearl Jam&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Wilco/status/885233478719221762&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Wilco&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/PearlJam/status/885230542576205824&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Wil Wheaton&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/TimRobbins1/status/885154464432136192&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tim Robbins&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/SusanSarandon/status/885196657792516097&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Susan Sarandon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/blues_traveler/status/885242752656605184&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Blues Traveler&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/stephenfry/status/884942083252920320&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Steven Fry&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/MarkRuffalo/status/885098668910444544&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Mark Ruffalo&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/LauraJaneGrace/status/885226732369960964&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Laura Jane Grace&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/kendrick38/status/885159414902042628&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Kendrick Sampson&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://consequenceofsound.net/2017/07/ted-leo-and-amanda-palmer-explain-why-we-need-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Amanda Palmer&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://consequenceofsound.net/2017/07/ted-leo-and-amanda-palmer-explain-why-we-need-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Ted Leo&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/FullFrontalSamB/status/885257665924018176&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Samantha Bee&lt;/a&gt;, and many more.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Broad participation from every corner of the Internet:&lt;/b&gt; from online gaming communities to librarians to real estate sites to grassroots organizations to independent musicians. &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/vYVet&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;See a gallery here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOTE: The volume of participation was so high that the FCC has been “rate limiting” submissions into their docket&lt;/b&gt; &amp;ndash; there are an enormous number of comments queued up that will be submitted into their system before the July 17 deadline, as fast as their system can handle them. The same is true for emails to Congress members, which will be delivered in the days to come.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Facebook, Google, and Dropbox&lt;/b&gt; three of the largest Internet companies, came out publicly with strong statements in support of the current FCC rules. This is significant &amp;ndash; especially given Facebook’s previous opposition to certain net neutrality rules, notably in India.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future, one of the leading groups behind the protest, issued the following statement (pronouns: she/hers): &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This was a historic moment when the Internet is realizing it’s power—with massive amounts of creative activism spreading to every corner of the Internet, from the smallest and weirdest nooks and crannies of the web to the most popular websites on earth. And this doesn’t end today—this protest is the kickoff of a sustained campaign to keep the pressure on lawmakers and the FCC to do the right thing. This is just our opening salvo, and it’s a massive one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The FCC needs to listen to the public, not just lobbyists from big cable companies. No one wants companies like Comcast, AT&amp;amp;T, and Verizon to have control over what we can see and do online, or to have to pay them extra fees to access the content we want. The Internet is outraged by censorship and corruption, this is our moment to to defend net neutrality and fight for the future of freedom of expression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Lawmakers in Washington, DC need to understand that if they stand idly by and allow the FCC to gut these rules that are overwhelmingly supported by voters from across the political spectrum, they will be seen as enemies of the Internet and enemies of free speech.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Pierce Stanley, technology fellow at Demand Progress, which co-led the effort: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Today, the largest web platforms in the world, scrappy activist organizations, and individuals from across the political spectrum came together online and in-person to make their voices heard. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Americans took to the internet to stand up for the rights to communicate freely, to organize, and to innovate online.  Ajit Pai’s plan to undermine net neutrality and stifle online speech would endanger these ways we use the internet, and could even make it harder &amp;ndash; or impossible &amp;ndash; to organize protests like today’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Ajit Pai may think big cable’s interests are more important than the public’s, but today’s activism makes it clear that few outside the boardrooms of Comcast or AT&amp;amp;T agree. A large majority of Americans of all political persuasions support net neutrality, and their voices were heard loud and clear. Today was the first step in taking back the internet from Pai and his cable cabal.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Candace Clement, campaign director for Free Press Action Fund, which co-led the effort:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“People used the internet to save the internet today. That’s because the Trump FCC’s push to ​destroy​ ​Net Neutrality's​ ​legal foundation​ ​isn&amp;rsquo;t fooling anyone​. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“We know that the open internet is critical for marginalized communities that ​​corporate media have misrepresented; that it’s essential for free speech and political organizing online; and that tech entrepreneurs need an open network to survive just as much as working families​ do​. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“Today we all joined together to stop FCC Chairman Pai’s quest to destroy the Net Neutrality safeguards that are ​crucial​ to everyone’s right to connect and communicate. And we’re going to stick with this fight for as long as it takes to preserve the open internet protections the majority of Americans demand.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Malkia Cyril, executive director of the Center for Media Justice which co-led the effort, said:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Today, thousands of people of color and civil rights leaders raised our voices to say loud and clear: we won&amp;rsquo;t let our internet become like cable TV, a white, middle class, and male bastion where we are shouted down daily. We&amp;rsquo;ll keep joining with allies of all kinds across the lines of difference to fight for our digital voice, and ensure that an open Internet protected by Title II net neutrality delivers political power and economic opportunity for those long excluded from both. The stakes are too high to do anything less.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The effort is led by many of the grassroots groups behind the largest online protests in history including the SOPA blackout and the &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com/infographic&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Internet Slowdown&lt;/a&gt;. Media attention for online mobilizations tends to focus on the big names participating, but there is a much more interesting story: a coalition of Internet activists huddled over their laptops in coworking spaces, home offices, and coffee shops, who are the ones who came up with the idea, called for, and organized the protest, and have since been working together to lay the groundwork, build the technical tools, and create the educational resources that make it possible for large and small websites to participate in these mass days of action. It’s a grassroots effort involving dozens of volunteers working together in Slack channels, outreach spreadsheets, endless email chains, organizing in online communities and forums, and an enormous amount of creativity and digital elbow grease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The list of sites and apps participating has grown so quickly it’s almost impossible to keep up, but participants include Automattic (Wordpress), eBay, Rosetta Stone, Pinterest, Amazon, Mozilla, Netflix, Etsy, Kickstarter, Soundcloud, Dropbox, Spotify, Redfin, Facebook, Google, Snapchat, Medium, Y Combinator, GitHub, Pantheon, Opera, Bittorrent Inc., Shapeways, Nextdoor, Stack Overflow, Funny Or Die, Dreamhost, and CREDO Mobile, Goldenfrog, Fark, Chess.com, Namecheap, DuckDuckGo, Checkout.com, Sonic, Ting, ProtonMail, O’Reilly Media, SlashDot, Dribble, Dischord, SourceForge, and Union Square Ventures. Organizations participating include Fight for the Future, Free Press Action Fund, Demand Progress, Center for Media Justice, EFF,  Internet Association, Internet Archive, World Wide Web Foundation, Creative Commons, National Hispanic Media Coalition, Greenpeace, Common Cause, ACLU, Rock the Vote, American Library Association, Daily Kos, OpenMedia, The Nation, PCCC, MoveOn, OFA, Public Knowledge, OTI, Color of Change, MoveOn, Free Software Foundation, Internet Creators Guild, the Women’s March, and many others.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 12:01:37 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-13-update-historic-day-of-action-for-net-neutrality/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-13-update-historic-day-of-action-for-net-neutrality/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Historic day of action for Net Neutrality breaks records: more than 1.6 million comments heading to FCC, 3 million+ emails and phone calls to Congress, well over 10 million people reached so far, as of 7:00pm</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;748&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1399&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://78.media.tumblr.com/eba973f468853ba9a79db6aaec538e4a/tumblr_inline_ot02v7QZop1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;748&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1399&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, July 12, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;More than 125,000 websites, Internet users, and organizations are participating in a massive online protest against the FCC’s plan to gut protections that keep the web free from censorship, throttling, and extra fees. Protesters gathering in DC and other cities, celebs weigh in&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of the most popular websites on the web have been participating in a historic Internet-Wide &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com/july12&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Day of Action&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;to Save Net Neutrality today to oppose the FCC’s plan to slash Title II, the legal foundation for net neutrality rules that protect online free speech and innovation. A flood of major web platforms like Twitter, Reddit, Netflix, Spotify, 4chan, Airbnb, Amazon, Mozilla, OK Cupid, Vimeo, Tinder, Expedia, Pornhub, Imgur, Yelp, and Soundcloud displayed prominent protest messages to their users, encouraging them to take action by contacting the FCC and Congress through tools like &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;BattleForTheNet.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;that make it easy for Internet users to make their voices heard. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See PHOTOS, IMAGES, and DESCRIPTIONS of how participants are protesting here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/vYVet&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://imgur.com/a/vYVet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There has been such a surge in activity &amp;ndash; and the traffic is not showing signs of slowing down &amp;ndash; that organizers are still scrambling to document everything that has happened but so far through the BattleForTheNet.com site alone (not including the Internet Association’s page or other aligned efforts) we’ve seen:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;IMPORTANT NOTE: these numbers represent only a portion of the final totals, and due to the massive numbers, comments and emails will be delivered over several days.  We will release additional updates as we continue documenting what has happened:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Well over 10 million people saw the protest messages&lt;/b&gt; on participating websites&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;3,450,000+ emails to Congress&lt;/b&gt; (which will be delivered over coming days)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;More than 1.6 million comments to the FCC&lt;/b&gt; (breaking our Sept. 10th 2014 “Internet Slowdown” record for most in a single day)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;#NetNeutrality trended on both Facebook and Twitter&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;More than 125,000 websites, people, artists, online creators, and organizations signed up to participate&lt;/b&gt; in the initial call to protest&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Celebrities flocked to support the effort &lt;/b&gt;including &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/PearlJam/status/885230542576205824&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pearl Jam&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/PearlJam/status/885230542576205824&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Wil Wheaton&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/TimRobbins1/status/885154464432136192&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tim Robbins&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/SusanSarandon/status/885196657792516097&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Susan Sarandon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/blues_traveler/status/885242752656605184&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Blues Traveler&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/stephenfry/status/884942083252920320&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Steven Fry&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/MarkRuffalo/status/885098668910444544&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Mark Ruffalo&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/LauraJaneGrace/status/885226732369960964&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Laura Jane Grace&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/kendrick38/status/885159414902042628&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Kendrick Sampson&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://consequenceofsound.net/2017/07/ted-leo-and-amanda-palmer-explain-why-we-need-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Amanda Palmer&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://consequenceofsound.net/2017/07/ted-leo-and-amanda-palmer-explain-why-we-need-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Ted Leo&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/FullFrontalSamB/status/885257665924018176&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Samantha Bee&lt;/a&gt;, and many more.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Broad participation from every corner of the Internet:&lt;/b&gt; from online gaming communities to librarians to real estate sites to grassroots organizations to independent musicians.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;NOTE: The volume of participation was so high that the FCC has been “rate limiting” submissions into their docket &amp;ndash; there are an enormous number of comments queued up that will be submitted into their system before the July 17 deadline, as fast as their system can handle them. The same is true for emails to Congress members, which will be delivered in the days to come.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Embed a video about the day of action here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DcIFBb3e3tFA%26feature%3Dyoutu.be&amp;amp;t=MGY2YThjMzU5MTMyMWQzMzEwNmVkYzk4ZmUyODViZTBmMDA1NzgxZixBdTdLV0dLRA%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F162821217028%2Flargest-websites-on-earth-prepare-for-net&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cIFBb3e3tFA&amp;amp;feature=youtu.be&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More highlights in this Twitter moment: &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/i/moments/885130181039579136&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/i/moments/885130181039579136&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future, one of the leading groups behind the protest, issued the following statement (pronouns: she/hers): &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“Today is a historic moment when the Internet is realizing it’s power—with massive amounts of creative activism spreading to every corner of the Internet, from the smallest and weirdest nooks and crannies of the web to the most popular websites on earth. And this doesn’t end today—this protest is the kickoff of a sustained campaign to keep the pressure on lawmakers and the FCC to do the right thing. This is just our opening salvo, and it’s a massive one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The FCC needs to listen to the public, not just lobbyists from big cable companies. No one wants companies like Comcast, AT&amp;amp;T, and Verizon to have control over what we can see and do online, or to have to pay them extra fees to access the content we want. The Internet is outraged by censorship and corruption, this is our moment to to defend net neutrality and fight for the future of freedom of expression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Lawmakers in Washington, DC need to understand that if they stand idly by and allow the FCC to gut these rules that are overwhelmingly supported by voters from across the political spectrum, they will be seen as enemies of the Internet and enemies of free speech.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Pierce Stanley, technology fellow at Demand Progress, which co-led the effort: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Today, the largest web platforms in the world, scrappy activist organizations, and individuals from across the political spectrum came together online and in-person to make their voices heard. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Americans took to the internet to stand up for the rights to communicate freely, to organize, and to innovate online.  Ajit Pai’s plan to undermine net neutrality and stifle online speech would endanger these ways we use the internet, and could even make it harder &amp;ndash; or impossible &amp;ndash; to organize protests like today’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Ajit Pai may think big cable’s interests are more important than the public’s, but today’s activism makes it clear that few outside the boardrooms of Comcast or AT&amp;amp;T agree. A large majority of Americans of all political persuasions support net neutrality, and their voices were heard loud and clear. Today was the first step in taking back the internet from Pai and his cable cabal.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Candace Clement, campaign director for Free Press Action Fund, which co-led the effort:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“People used the internet to save the internet today. That’s because the Trump FCC’s push to ​destroy​ ​Net Neutrality's​ ​legal foundation​ ​isn&amp;rsquo;t fooling anyone​. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“We know that the open internet is critical for marginalized communities that ​​corporate media have misrepresented; that it’s essential for free speech and political organizing online; and that tech entrepreneurs need an open network to survive just as much as working families​ do​. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“Today we all joined together to stop FCC Chairman Pai’s quest to destroy the Net Neutrality safeguards that are ​crucial​ to everyone’s right to connect and communicate. And we’re going to stick with this fight for as long as long as it takes to preserve the open internet protections the majority of Americans demand.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Malkia Cyril, executive director of the Center for Media Justice which co-led the effort, said:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Today, thousands of people of color and civil rights leaders raised our voices to say loud and clear: we won&amp;rsquo;t let our internet become like cable TV, a white, middle class, and male bastion where we are shouted down daily. We&amp;rsquo;ll keep joining with allies of all kinds across the lines of difference to fight for our digital voice, and ensure that an open Internet protected by Title II net neutrality delivers political power and economic opportunity for those long excluded from both. The stakes are too high to do anything less.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The effort is led by many of the grassroots groups behind the largest online protests in history including the SOPA blackout and the &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com/infographic&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Internet Slowdown&lt;/a&gt;. Media attention for online mobilizations tends to focus on the big names participating, but there is a much more interesting story: a coalition of Internet activists huddled over their laptops in coworking spaces, home offices, and coffee shops, who are the ones who came up with the idea, called for, and organized the protest, and have since been working together to lay the groundwork, build the technical tools, and create the educational resources that make it possible for large and small websites to participate in these mass days of action. It’s a grassroots effort involving dozens of volunteers working together in Slack channels, outreach spreadsheets, endless email chains, organizing in online communities and forums, and an enormous amount of creativity and digital elbow grease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The list of sites and apps participating has grown so quickly it’s almost impossible to keep up, but participants include Automattic (Wordpress), eBay, Rosetta Stone, Pinterest, Amazon, Mozilla, Netflix, Etsy, Kickstarter, Soundcloud, Dropbox, Spotify, Redfin, Facebook, Google, Snapchat, Medium, Y Combinator, GitHub, Pantheon, Opera, Bittorrent Inc., Shapeways, Nextdoor, Stack Overflow, Funny Or Die, Dreamhost, and CREDO Mobile, Goldenfrog, Fark, Chess.com, Namecheap, DuckDuckGo, Checkout.com, Sonic, Ting, ProtonMail, O’Reilly Media, SlashDot, Dribble, Dischord, SourceForge, and Union Square Ventures. Organizations participating include Fight for the Future, Free Press Action Fund, Demand Progress, Center for Media Justice, EFF,  Internet Association, Internet Archive, World Wide Web Foundation, Creative Commons, National Hispanic Media Coalition, Greenpeace, Common Cause, ACLU, Rock the Vote, American Library Association, Daily Kos, OpenMedia, The Nation, PCCC, MoveOn, OFA, Public Knowledge, OTI, Color of Change, MoveOn, Free Software Foundation, Internet Creators Guild, the Women’s March, and many others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 19:06:46 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-12-historic-day-of-action-for-net-neutrality-breaks/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-12-historic-day-of-action-for-net-neutrality-breaks/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UPDATE: Massive protest for net neutrality spreads across the Internet</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;713&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1357&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://78.media.tumblr.com/eea02c4afd6799a15e47559f1e434ee2/tumblr_inline_oszpcmyZlK1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;713&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1357&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, July 12, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;More than 100,000  websites, Internet users, and organizations are participating in a massive online protest against the FCC’s plan to gut protections that keep the web free from censorship, throttling, and extra fees. Protesters have also gathered outside the Senate in DC.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of the most popular websites on the web are participating in an Internet-Wide &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com/july12&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Day of Action&lt;/a&gt; to Save Net Neutrality today to oppose the FCC’s plan to slash Title II, the legal foundation for net neutrality rules that protect online free speech and innovation. Starting at midnight, a flood of major web platforms like Twitter, Reddit, Netflix, Spotify, Airbnb, Amazon, Mozilla, OK Cupid, Vimeo, Pornhub, Imgur, and Soundcloud began displaying prominent protest messages to their users, encouraging them to take action by contacting the FCC and Congress through tools like &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;BattleForTheNet.com&lt;/a&gt; that make it easy for Internet users to make their voices heard. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See PHOTOS, IMAGES, and DESCRIPTIONS of how participants are protesting here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/vYVet&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://imgur.com/a/vYVet&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Embed a video about the day of action here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DcIFBb3e3tFA%26feature%3Dyoutu.be&amp;amp;t=MGY2YThjMzU5MTMyMWQzMzEwNmVkYzk4ZmUyODViZTBmMDA1NzgxZixBdTdLV0dLRA%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F162821217028%2Flargest-websites-on-earth-prepare-for-net&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cIFBb3e3tFA&amp;amp;feature=youtu.be&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;More highlights in this Twitter moment: &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/i/moments/885130181039579136&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/i/moments/885130181039579136&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future, one of the leading groups behind the protest, issued the following statement (pronouns: she/hers): &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;“Today is a historic moment when the Internet is realizing it’s power. We’re massive amounts of creativity and action coming from every corner of the Internet, from the smallest and weirdest nooks and crannies of the web to the most popular websites on earth. And this doesn’t end today &amp;ndash; this protest is the kickoff of a sustained campaign to keep the pressure on lawmakers and the FCC to do the right thing. This is our opening salvo, and it’s a massive one.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;The FCC needs to listen to the public, not just lobbyists from big cable companies. Today, the Internet is showing its political power. No one wants companies like Comcast, AT&amp;amp;T, and Verizon to have control over what we can see and do online, or to have to pay them extra fees to access the content we want. The Internet is outraged by censorship and corruption, this is our moment to to defend net neutrality and fight for the future of freedom of expression.”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Lawmakers in Washington, DC need to understand that if they stand idly by and allow the FCC to gut these rules that are overwhelmingly supported by voters from across the political spectrum, they will be seen as enemies of the Internet and enemies of free speech.”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;480&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;640&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://78.media.tumblr.com/1d2d99b4cdc180fb589fe7f674100b44/tumblr_inline_oszpd6HBJG1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;480&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;640&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than 100,000 people, sites, and organizations signed up to participate the effort ahead of the 12th, and many times that will have joined in by the end of the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The effort is led by many of the grassroots groups behind the largest online protests in history including the SOPA blackout and the &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com/infographic&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Internet Slowdown&lt;/a&gt;. Media attention for online mobilizations tends to focus on the big names participating, but there is a much more interesting story: a coalition of Internet activists huddled over their laptops in coworking spaces, home offices, and coffee shops, who are the ones who came up with the idea, called for, and organized the protest, and have since been working together to lay the groundwork, build the technical tools, and create the educational resources that make it possible for large and small websites to participate in these mass days of action. It’s a grassroots effort involving dozens of volunteers working together in Slack channels, outreach spreadsheets, endless email chains, organizing in online communities and forums, and an enormous amount of creativity and digital elbow grease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;928&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1604&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://78.media.tumblr.com/20d443c348116b62168ec81dbb8bb7e2/tumblr_inline_oszpdo9Wd11ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;928&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1604&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The list of sites and apps participating has grown so quickly it’s almost impossible to keep up, but participants include Automattic (Wordpress), eBay, Rosetta Stone, Pinterest, Amazon, Mozilla, Netflix, Etsy, Kickstarter, Soundcloud, Dropbox, Spotify, Facebook, Google, Snapchat, Medium, Y Combinator, GitHub, Pantheon, Opera, Bittorrent Inc., Shapeways, Nextdoor, Stack Overflow, Funny Or Die, Dreamhost, and CREDO Mobile, Goldenfrog, Fark, Chess.com, Namecheap, DuckDuckGo, Checkout.com, Sonic, Ting, ProtonMail, O’Reilly Media, SlashDot, Dribble, Dischord, SourceForge, and Union Square Ventures. Organizations participating include Fight for the Future, Free Press Action Fund, Demand Progress, Center for Media Justice, EFF,  Internet Association, Internet Archive, World Wide Web Foundation, Creative Commons, National Hispanic Media Coalition, Greenpeace, Common Cause, ACLU, Rock the Vote, American Library Association, Daily Kos, OpenMedia, The Nation, PCCC, MoveOn, OFA, Public Knowledge, OTI, Color of Change, MoveOn, Free Software Foundation, Internet Creators Guild, the Women’s March, and many others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;925&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1501&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://78.media.tumblr.com/8c2f6784606f30bdc4ca8584dacf20cf/tumblr_inline_oszpexGaNV1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;925&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1501&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 07:21:28 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-12-update-massive-protest-for-net-neutrality-spreads/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-12-update-massive-protest-for-net-neutrality-spreads/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>

